export const Questions=[
    {
        prompt:"Who sang the title song for the latest Bond film, No Time to Die?",
        optionA:"Adele",
        optionB:"Sam Smith",
        optionC:"Billie Eilish",
        answer: "optionC"
    },
    {
        prompt:"Which flies a green, white, and orange (in that order) tricolor flag?",
        optionA:"Ireland",
        optionB:"Ivory Coast",
        optionC:"Italy",
        answer:"optionA"
    },
    {
        prompt:"What company makes the Xperia model of smartphone?",
        optionA:"Samsung",
        optionB:"Sony",
        optionC:"Nokia",
        answer:"optionB"
    },
    {
        prompt:"Which city is home to the Brandenburg Gate?",
        optionA:"Vienna",
        optionB:"Zurich",
        optionC:"Berlin",
        answer:"optionC"
    },
    {
        prompt:"Where was the first example of paper money used?",
        optionA:"China",
        optionB:"Turkey",
        optionC:"Greece",
        answer:"optionA"
    },
    {
        prompt:"If you were looking at Iguazu Falls, on what continent would you be?",
        optionA:"Asia",
        optionB:"Africa",
        optionC:"South America",
        answer:"optionC"
    },
    {
        prompt:"What number was the Apollo mission that successfully put a man on the moon for the first time in human history? ",
        optionA:"Apollo 11",
        optionB:"Apollo 12",
        optionC:"Apollo 13",
        answer:"optionA"
    },
    {
        prompt:"Which of the following languages has the longest alphabet?",
        optionA:"Greek",
        optionB:"Russian",
        optionC:"Arabic",
        answer:"optionB"
    },
    {
        prompt:"Who was the lead singer of the band The Who?",
        optionA:"Roger Daltrey",
        optionB:"Don Henley",
        optionC:"Robert Plant",
        answer:"optionA"
    },
    {
        prompt:"Which horoscope sign is a fish?",
        optionA:"Aquarius",
        optionB:"Cancer",
        optionC:"Pisces",
        answer:"optionC"
    }

]
